const deck={
  Spanish: {
    title: 'Spanish',
  
  cards: [
    {
      question: 'Hola',
      answer:'Hello'
    },
    {
      question: 'Buenos Dias',
      answer:'Good Morning'
    },
    {
      question: 'Buenos noches',
      answer:'Good Night'
    },
    
    {
      question: 'Adios',
      answer:'Good Bye'
    },
    {
      question: 'Como estas?',
      answer:'How are you?'
    },
    {
      question: 'Rojo',
      answer:'Red'
    },
    {
      question: 'Azul',
      answer:'Blue'
    },
    {
      question: 'Verde',
      answer:'Green'
    },
    {
      question: 'Blanco',
      answer:'White'
    },
   
  ]
},

Japanese: {
  title: 'Japanese',

cards: [
  {
    question: 'Konichiwa',
    answer:'Hello'
  },
  {
    question: 'Ohayo',
    answer:'Good Morning'
  },
  {
    question: 'Konbawa',
    answer:'Good Night'
  },
  {
    question: 'Sayonara',
    answer:'Good Bye'
  },
  {
    question: 'O genki desuka?',
    answer:'How are you?'
  },
  {
    question: 'Aka',
    answer:'Red'
  },
  {
    question: 'Aoi',
    answer:'Blue'
  },
  {
    question: 'Midori',
    answer:'Green'
  },
  {
    question: 'Shiro',
    answer:'White'
  },
 
]
},

}

export default deck